babylegs.com 2017-09-21

# Leg warmers for babies & toddlers at BabyLegs - Privacy policy

**BABYLEGS div. of United Legwear & Apparel Co. (ULAC) **

**dba BabyLegs®**

The information we obtain from you is primarily for communication purposes and to assist us in serving you. Additionally it helps us to personalize and continually improve your user experience with BABYLEGS® products and services.

**Scope of Privacy Policy:** This Privacy Policy applies only to the personal information you provide and we collect through our Services. By "personal information," we mean information that identifies you personally. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and hereby made a part of the BABYLEGS® Terms of Use. You can view the Terms of Use at: [www.babylegs.com/terms-of-use](http://www.babylegs.com/terms-of-use/)

**Types of Information Gathered:** Through your use of our Services, we gather the following types of information:

**Information You Give Us:** We receive and securely store any information you enter on our Website or voluntarily provide to us in any manner, including your name, email address, mailing shipping and billing addresses and, for online purchases, credit card or other payment information. We may use this information to communicate with you. If you wish not to receive communications from us, please notify us via email at info@babylegs.com.

**Automatic Information:** By accessing our Website, certain information, such as

Internet protocol (IP) addresses, navigation through the Website, the software used and the time spent, along with other similar information, will be stored on our servers. These will not specifically identify you. The information will be used internally only for Website traffic analysis.

**Use of Cookies:** "Cookies" are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable us to customize your experience and store your preferences.

**Security of Personal Information:** BabyLegs® takes reasonable measures to secure your personal information from unauthorized use and disclosure both online and offline. Whenever we collect personal information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You may verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the Web page. While we use encryption to protect personal information online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computer(s) and servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment. With respect to credit card numbers, only the last four digits of your credit card number are visible on our system to our employees. However, please note that no website is completely immune from potential security breaches. In order to increase the security of your personal information, we highly recommend that you vigilantly guard your password. If you have reason to believe that your personal information has been accessed without your permission, please change your password immediately and notify us at info@babylegs.com.

BabyLegs® will never knowingly request personally identifiable information online from anyone under the age of 13 without prior verifiable parental consent. Our website is a general audience site and is not targeted to or intended for use by children.

**Information Shared with Third Parties:** We will not share your personal information with any third party. While we reserve the right to share aggregated non-personally identifiable information with third parties for any reason, we will not share your Personally Identifiable Information without your express consent. We may use your personal information without your prior consent when we have a good faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request, (b) enforce applicable Terms of Use, including investigation of potential violations thereof, (c) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, or (d) protect against imminent harm to the rights, property or safety of BABYLEGS®, its users or the public as required or permitted by law.

From time to time, we may supplement Personally Identifiable Information collected on our Website with information collected by third parties.

**Your Access and Control Over Information:** You may opt out of any future contact from us at any time. You may do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our Website:

  * See what data we have about you, if any;
  * Change or correct any data we have about you;
  * Have us delete any data we have about you; or
  * Express any concern you have about our use of your data.

**Changes and Updates to Privacy Policy and/or Terms of Use:** As our business changes, our Privacy Policy and Terms of Use will change as well. You should check our Website regularly for changes.
